<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Engels on GIP-Site 2015-2016 Ricardo Coenen</title>
    <link>http://ricardo-coenen.github.io:1313/GIPsite/engels/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Engels on GIP-Site 2015-2016 Ricardo Coenen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://ricardo-coenen.github.io:1313/GIPsite/engels/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Task 13: Review of a software tool in the training company</title>
      <link>http://ricardo-coenen.github.io:1313/GIPsite/review.png</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ricardo-coenen.github.io:1313/GIPsite/review.png</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;review-of-a-software-tool-in-the-training-company-ricardo-coenen:2cd397b25e1ccda644282ccdbd547c8a&#34;&gt;Review of a software tool in the training company: Ricardo Coenen&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For my review of today, I am going to review AXIS Camera Companion (ACC). The reception of my internship used it to watch all entries and it records everything that happens. Most of the time, they use it for surveillance of their building and cars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ACC is software designed by AXIS communications which also creates cameras and camera systems. You can use the tool to control all the cameras you have. There is a lot of other software on the market you can use to control your cameras, but the ACC is free. You can buy extra packages for the software like: event detection, ANPR, fire detection, … . The software has an easy install wizard. You can expand the software as much as you want (remote camera control, recording, …).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First of all, the best thing about the tool is that it is free. The free version has a lot of cool features you can use in your company, or at home. However, the upgrades you can buy are pretty expensive. I think that almost every brand of camera can be used in this software, is an advantage. You can even use a webcam and use ACC! However, if you want to make sure there won’t be any complications, it’s recommended that you buy the cameras from AXIS Communications. As said before, the software has an easy install wizard, and you don’t need to be an advanced user to use it. You can learn the whole program in a small amount of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are also a couple of minor annoyances: if you want the software to run smoothly, you have to buy the cameras of AXIS. These cameras aren’t cheap at all (€ 8,000 per camera). As you can see, a normal household couldn’t buy this kind of cameras. It also fails sometimes in recording. If you have bought the event detection package, it sometimes won’t record events. It always detects an event and normally it should automatically start recording and saving, but most of the times that won’t happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think this software, in combination with the cameras of AXIS, is currently the best on the market. It has everything you need, and it is easy to use. I agree with the review that it is definitely a winner. I would give this software a &lt;sup&gt;10&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt; although the software fails sometimes in recording events. But thankfully, there is a support helpdesk that will help you very fast, and provides updates fast. Maybe, by the time of writing this, they have already released an update in which they fixed that problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would recommend this software to other companies which have the budget to buy the cameras with the software. I think companies like banks should buy it, because AXIS also have cameras which are explosion proof. So if you want to secure your company or house, make sure you have the camera system of AXIS Communications.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Task 03: Instructionvideo Sway English</title>
      <link>http://ricardo-coenen.github.io:1313/GIPsite/it-tapa.jpg</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ricardo-coenen.github.io:1313/GIPsite/it-tapa.jpg</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;sway-instructionvideo:df2f7b215446a57c38925e3eae29616e&#34;&gt;Sway Instructionvideo&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/57pRtsp7SI4&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Task 05: IT-Autobiography</title>
      <link>http://ricardo-coenen.github.io:1313/GIPsite/autobiography.png</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ricardo-coenen.github.io:1313/GIPsite/autobiography.png</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;it-autobiography-of-ricardo-coenen:b8ba8b1fcf0c24f1bbf715390a897859&#34;&gt;IT-Autobiography of Ricardo Coenen&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome reader, I&amp;rsquo;m Ricardo Coenen, student at the Immaculata Institute and currently studying IT-management. I&amp;rsquo;m the &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;fixer&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;. When someone has a question or something is broken, they ask me for help, most of the time. I will not continue in IT-management after this year, I hope to join the police or army.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was 10 when I started playing with computers. I got an old computer from my mother and I started googling, investigating and tried a lot of things. At a certain point I searched the web, and found that you can hack other people. At that moment, my mother met a new partner and he taught me everything I needed to know. You can&amp;rsquo;t imagine how happy I was about being able to hack a site. He told me that I can only use that &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;power&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt; for skills or good things, not bad things. So over all these years, I am learning a lot of computers, not just from Google, but a lot from my stepfather.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And still, I can learn from my stepfather. I still learn something new from him every week. IT means so much for me now. I sometimes think about it, and what would have become of me when my mother hadn&amp;rsquo;t met my step-dad. When I&amp;rsquo;m home, I&amp;rsquo;m behind my computer most of the time. It&amp;rsquo;s relaxing for me, as football can be relaxing for someone else. When working on my computer, I like building sites, expanding our network, building server in our network, etc&amp;hellip; . I think I&amp;rsquo;m lucky that my dad let me all do it, he even pays new stuff so I can experiment with new devices, software and hardware. At the moment I don&amp;rsquo;t game much, but when I play a game, it&amp;rsquo;s mostly fps-games. I have made multiple networks, repaired computers, hosted servers and designed multiple sites of which I still manage one . The site is still under construction, but it has already been published. I don&amp;rsquo;t see myself as an expert, but I think I can say I know a lot of the basic stuff of IT and pretty much of hacking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like I said, I don&amp;rsquo;t see myself programming software or building networks. I hope I can join the police or army, if not, I would like to learn everything about hacking. I know there is a school which specialises in hacking, but unfortunately it&amp;rsquo;s a school in a foreign country. I know there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of business in the IT-security industry, because nowadays, everything is online, and everything is hackable, so there will always be a need for IT-security. I just hope I will never have to look at a screen every day of my life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;img/portfolio/ik.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>